module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What is the title of the song the begins "Chestnuts roasting on a fire"?', 
    a: 'Chestnuts Roasting on an Open Fire',
    b: 'Merry Christmas',
    c: 'The Christmas Song',
    d: 'Many Times Many Ways',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What made Frosty the Snowman come to life?', 
    a: 'An old silk hat',
    b: 'A corncob pipe',
    c: 'A broomstick in his hand',
    d: 'A button nose',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT one of Santa\'s reindeer?', 
    a: 'Blitzen',
    b: 'Comet',
    c: 'Connor',
    d: 'Vixen',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many lamps did the menorah in the Temple have?', 
    a: '7',
    b: '8',
    c: '9',
    d: '12',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Celebration of the Jewish New Year is known as what?', 
    a: 'Purim',
    b: 'Yom Kippur',
    c: 'Ramadan',
    d: 'Rosh Hashana',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'In what year did the New Year\'s Eve Ball first drop in Time\'s Square?', 
    a: '1900',
    b: '1907',
    c: '1910',
    d: '1917',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does the Hebrew word Chanukah mean?', 
    a: 'Peace',
    b: 'Love',
    c: 'Dedication',
    d: 'Perserverence',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the candle used to light all the others during Hanukkah?', 
    a: 'Shamash',
    b: 'Shann-Wow',
    c: 'Shaman',
    d: 'Smashley',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'How fast does an average snowflake fall?', 
    a: '4 mph',
    b: '3 mph',
    c: '2 mph',
    d: '1 mph',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many sides does every single snowflake have?', 
    a: '4',
    b: '6',
    c: '8',
    d: '10',
    answer: 'c'
  },
];